Personal Information

Name: Mohmad Gamal Ali Mohmad

Email: mohmadgamal454@gmail.com

Mobile: +201223072359

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mohmad-gamal-196943168

GitHub: https://github.com/Mohmad012

Portfolio: https://mohmad012.github.io/Main Portfolio/

Career Objective

A Software Engineer who seeks an opportunity as a Frontend Developer to improve my skills and to be part of an organization where I can contribute my skills to the organization's growth. Also, I am an expert in building UI components using react, managing application state using Redux, Rendering App on the server using next.js, handling client-side routing using React-router-dom.

Education

2016-2020

Bachelor's Degree, Faculty of Science, Al-Azhar University.

Experience

June 2022 – Present

Frontend Developer

Startup Defenders - Full Time

Working in Scrum Environment With Saferoad Dashboard Including:

- Handling millions of record data incoming Daily from Firebase Real Time Database
- Manipulation those data on Google Map
- Debugging With VS Code.

https://www.saferoad.com.sa/

March 2021 - May 2022

Frontend Developer

Freelancer

Projects

• E-commerce App

<u>Description</u>: An e-commerce website that allows users to sell and buy products by implementing features like Amazon.com.

Buy & Sale App

Technologies: React.js, Redux ToolKit, Styled Components, AJAX, Material-UI,

AOS, Stripe, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, JWT.

Live URL: https://frontend-e-commerce-app.vercel.app/

Code URL: https://github.com/Mohmad012/Full E-Commerce App

Online Store App

Technologies: React.JS, Next.JS, Redux, SASS, AJAX, PayPal SDK.

<u>Live URL:</u> https://store-shop-phi.vercel.app/ <u>Code URL:</u> https://github.com/Mohmad012/Store Shop

• TVFLIX

<u>Description</u>: A website that allows users for search to about any movie by using API to get

more information about the movie that the user searches.

Technologies: React.js, React-Router, and AJAX.

<u>Live URL: https://mohmad012.github.io/TV_Search_Flix/</u>
Code URL: https://github.com/Mohmad012/TV_Search_Flix

• Company Website

Description: A website that shows the company's data.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

<u>Live URL: https://mohmad012.github.io/web_pure_Javascript/</u>
<u>Code URL: https://github.com/Mohmad012/web_pure_Javascript</u>

Technical Skills and Conceptual Knowledge

• JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS,.

- Bootstrap, Material-UI, SASS.
- React.JS, Next.JS, Redux, ContextAPI
- AJAX, Git (Git Flow) As Version Control.
- Webpack, Parcel, Grunt.js, Gulp.js As Task Runner.
- Node.js, and Express.js, PostgreSQL database, MongoDB, JWT
- Socket.io.
- Stripe
- Firebase Real Time, Google Map, Debugging With VS Code.
- Unit Test

Additional Info

Military Service: Finished

Languages: Arabic (Native)

English (Very good)